<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gergő&#39;s Phlog</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gergő&#39;s Phlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 20:19:06 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Holiday funkies 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-11-24-holiday-funkies-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 20:19:06 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-11-24-holiday-funkies-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No special description this time: random street-style photos from a recent holiday in Italy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remains of the 1956 Olympic ski jump ramp</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-09-06-cortina/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 19:09:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-09-06-cortina/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Situated in the Dolomites of Italy, Cortina d’Ampezzo hosted the 1956 Winter Olympics. When visiting the town in 2024, we discovered the old ramp used for ski jumping. While far from being an expert, I believe the ramp is not in use anymore. I particularly liked the twist of repurposing of the landing strip into a local football field.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two photographs, September 2024&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roof of Amsterdam&#39;s central bus station</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-06-15-adam-roof/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 20:19:24 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-06-15-adam-roof/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The bus terminal of Amsterdam’s central station is elevated above ground. When coming up on an escalator, my attention is drawn to the terminal’s glass roof. It is covered with an alternating mix of wine-red and mustard coloured tiles. At first, the arrangement seems random, or abstract at best. Only after some observation – made possible by my delayed bus – do (flipped) letters start to take shape: M, A, D, R. While the rest of them disappear in the distance of the platform, I have lived long enough in the Netherlands to figure it out: when viewed from above, such as a landing airplane, the terminal’s roof displays A-M-S-T-E-R-D-A-M.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luchtsingel, Rotterdam</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-03-09-luchtsingel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 19:10:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-03-09-luchtsingel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My takes during a walk on the one and only ‘yellow bridge’ of Rotterdam – on a serene and sunny early spring morning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those who don’t know about this remarkable piece of public infrastructure, it’s essentially a octopus-like pedestrian high-way that connects three districts in the center of Rotterdam.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sculpture of Nike in sunset</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-02-09-nike-sculpture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-02-09-nike-sculpture/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nike was goddess of victory in ancient Greece. This sculpture of her was first erected in the Agora of Athens around 425 BC. Originally carved as winged on her back, a typical representation of Nike, she has lost her wings at some point over the millenia. In this photo, I attempted to create an illusion for this irreplacable loss using the light and shadows of the setting sun in Athens.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Parthenon in three frames</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-02-08-parthenon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:09:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/minors/2024-02-08-parthenon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Owing to its architecture, decorations, and location in the heart of Athens, the Parthenon is a major cultural symbol of Greece. While any building aged 2500 years would happily be in the condition of the Parthenon, it has certainly lost some of its beauty over the years; damages caused both by nature and humans. These three frames are my reflections on the present state and remaining grace of this ancient masterpiece.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Orbit</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/majors/in-orbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:52:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/majors/in-orbit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content of second album.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Do You See</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/majors/what-do-you-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 15:52:16 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/majors/what-do-you-see/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content of first album.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
